The light should rest now.
Uncle!
Awake, are ya?
You guys did it!
Where is Liana?
I'm over here!
Liana!
We can't keep delaying things!
We may not be able to escape
from this place!
What the-
Where did the submarine go?
Those black suits must've run off with it.
Damn it...
Z-Z-Zenigata?
I've found you, Lupin!
What are you doin' here, Pops?
I found your friends
and they showed me
where you were underwater.
Then I found this
and thought you were here.
But it was people
who kidnapped the children
for "Power".
Well, I guess you win again, Pops.
In any case, we're saved.
C'mon you two.
Yes!
Liana?
Liana? What's wrong?
It's my mother.
Huh?
I was giving thanks to my mother
for the light.
The light?
I got to see my mother
in the Oceanfolk's light.
She's the one who told me
to seal this place.
So no one else
could touch it again.
But, if we don't hurry-
Hey!
Gotta hurry if we wanna get outta here!
You're not getting away this time!
I get it already.
Ready?
Yes.