We're 28 meters deep.
Keep it steady.
Do you see anything?
There is no change in the monitor.
We should be close by.
Proceed with caution.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Claustrophobic, are you?
Some hero you are.
There must be one or two
things that you're afraid of!
Aren't you the energetic one?
What's that?
Looks to be a gigantic
blue hole ahead of us.
Blue hole?
It's like a limestone cavern
at the bottom of the sea.
The inside is uncharted and dangerous.
Descent into it.
Huh? I mean... that's...
The location indicated by the Kirim
is inside of here.
So please, enter it.
Y-yes sir.
Visibility is at 50.
It's quite creepy here.
We're at depth 41, 42...
Currently 43 meters,
and still descending.
This seems never ending.
What's going on?
What's wrong?
The water temperature
is rising rapidly.
86, 96, 104 degrees.
The water temperature?
Also, moisture levels in the sea water
are 50 more
than the average.
Is it an underwater volcano?
Okay, the kids are right below me.
But, man, what's up with this hole?
The water's gotten hotter
all of a sudden.
It's like a hot spring in here.
If it weren't for this suit, I'd be in trouble.
Huh?
What's wrong??
There's a strong current!
It's too dangerous to keep going!
Just keep going!
We must follow the Kirim's direction!
An ominous hole...
A bottomless drop...
Theo, do you remember
the sleeping dragon story?
What are you mumbling about?!
Shut up!
Liana!
Quiet kid, I don't care about you!
Now talk! What were you saying!?
If you're an Oceanfolk
then you should know
the sleeping dragon story.
The what?
The sleeping dragon
at the end of the world.
I get it. It was talking about Saludo.
Start talking plainly.
Don't pretend you never heard of it.
Your mother or father never told you?
What?
What happened?
The tide is changing even more!
I can't control the sub now!
Nothing is broken in the sub.
The water temperature is back to normal.
Okay.
Finally awake, are you?
Liana, what's going on?
The Dragon's Fang.
The Dragon's Fang...
That is the sleeping dragon,
the sacred home
of the Oceanfolk, Saludo.
So, this is the entrance?
Yes.
The fangs, in this case,
are likely the Kirims.
The Kirims take the place of a key.
Have you really never heard the story?
Give me the Kirims, and I'll open it.
Don't try anything funny.
Don't forget, he's still here.
Don't worry.
I'll keep my word.
Man, what a rough swim.
So this must be the entrance to Saludo.
Amazing... The light is beautiful.
The air is pure here, too.
Liana!
So this is Saludo...
Liana.
This must be the dragon's belly,
full of beautiful scales.
Huh?
The stories were all true.
You're right.
Enough sightseeing.
You have to show us around the place.
I'm not some tour guide!
I've never even been here!
You seem to bring up the story often...
I really didn't know anything, up until now...
I thought it was nothing more
than a bedtime story.
But this is the first time I've been here.
Well, this is our home now, so
we must explore the place.
Two of you guys, stay here.
Yes sir!
But why is there light down here?
And oxygen too?
I can't explain the light, but the oxygen
was made from stromatolites
2 billion years ago.
It's claimed the plant
created all the oxygen currently on Earth.
Quite magnificent, isn't it?
Another boat is approaching us.
Look who it is.
Where is Lupin?
He's a little busy.
Where are the kidnappers?
Went this way, then went that way.
I see, so Lupin went into the ocean?
Don't you think you're overdoing things?
Mind your business, I'm scuba trained!
I'll dive down there to catch Lupin if I must!
Pray for me that I won't be eaten by sharks!
Hope you don't get eaten by sharks.
Amazing...
Liana... what is this stuff?
Hey!
What's the meaning of this?
There's a lot of stones here...
maybe this is the graveyard
for the Oceanfolk?
A grave?
These stones are graves?
A tomb for the Oceanfolk?
Is that it?
We can't stop now! There must be a way...
The legend must be more than a stone!
This wasn't in the damned legend!
Where could it be?
I don't know anything.
Don't play dumb!
Where is the great power?
What are you looking for?
What do you think
the great power actually is?
You little brat!
Liana!
Stop!
Please... stop it...
I think I understand.
Saludo is a cemetery for the Oceanfolk.
Don't you feel it, too?
The desire to rest in peace undisturbed,
one with the ocean?
That wish led
to the building of this place, Saludo.
The great power doesn't exist.
For the last time...
Tell me where the great power is.
I told you!
It doesn't exist!
Is that so?
Your're a monster...
I won't ask again. Where is it?
Where is the great power?
The great power of Saludo.
Behind the dragon's frozen tears.
What?
Probably past the stalactites up ahead.
I see.
Then you can lead the way. Come this way.
Good girl. Shall we get going?
You two, wait here with the boy.
Yes sir!
Theo...
Theo.
Theo!
Uncle...?
Are you okay, Theo?
How did you get here?
That's right, Liana... Where's Liana?
It's likely Zai took her.
Now is not the time to be sitting down.
Get up, Theo, we have to save Liana!
Yes!
The frozen heart...
Is this the great power!?
Now, how do I use the Kirims, Minupa?
Kirims? What are you talking about?
They're still stuck in the entrance.
You should know that.
Don't you worry about that!
Now, how do I use them?
You can't! If the dragon runs wild,
something awful will happen.
Tell me!
No!
Liana...
Theo, what's wrong?
I just heard Liana's voice!
We have to hurry!
OK!
Stubborn girl. No matter.
Once I've obtained the power,
I'll take my time dealing with you.
The Kirims are reacting!
This is it! I finally found it!
Don't!
This is it! This light!
The light that even God fears!
The great power is in my grasp!
At this rate, we're done for!
Jigen, look over there.
Huh?
What the...?
Don't tell me this is the great power!
Liana!
Theo! Lupin!
Liana! I'm coming!
Don't come here!
You two stay away from the light.
If anyone other than an Oceanfolk touches this light,
they'll be evaporated!
Magnificent!
It's finally mine! The great power!
What is this?
What's happening?
Why am I-
Liana!
Theo! I'm glad you're safe!
Are you okay too, Liana?
Yes, I'm fine!
Sorry to break up this touching reunion,
but we should hurry and get out of here.
You two go ahead. There's something
important I have to do first.
What are you talking about, Liana?
What's so important at this moment?
That.
Huh?
The frozen heart. It's starting to melt.
Soon, something terrible will happen.
It must be sealed before then.
Then, I'll go with you!
No! You can't come with me!
I already told you, if you're not an Oceanfolk,
you'll be evaporated too!
No way, Liana. It's too dangerous.
That's right!
Don't worry, I'll be fine! I'm a Minupa!
Liana...
I'll go with you!
She's a Minupa so she'll protect me!
Guess there's no helping you kids.
I guess you can go with her.
I bet she will protect you, no matter what.
But if it gets too dangerous,
I'll bring you back.
Yes!
You pulled out the Kirims,
but nothing changed.
Taking out the Kirims won't seal it.
We have to insert them in the opposite way.
Got it.